ここは墓場。
There are six distinct categories of Nen users.
貴様のな。
Enhancer. Enhancers are able to strengthen
various objects' effectiveness.
感謝するぜ
Emitter. Emitters can propel their
aura like projectiles.
お前と出会えた これまでの全てに！
Specialist. Specialists are those with rare abilities
that don't fit in the other five classes.
はっ！
This place is much harder
to find than you realize.
王は　極限まで時が圧縮され
You found the agency on your own, so you must be pretty sharp.
意識のみが　辛うじて捉える ネテロの残像を追いながら
But I can't recommend you to
one of our valued clients.
ある感情に支配されていた
I have no problem with your lack of experience. Some clients don't mind greenhorns.
敵への惜しみなき称賛
I said that I have a Hunter License! But your exam hasn't ended yet.
これだ 両の手のひらを合わせ 攻撃への起点とする所作
Once you've learned to see, return.
何故　奴が これを体得するに至ったか
You can't see it, but you can sense it.
考察することに意味はない
Why did you do that?!
到底　合理的な道筋では たどり着けない場所だからだ
This? Well, I was just playing with you.
恐らくは　狂気にすら 近い感情に身を委ねたのだ
Fate had a hand in crossing our paths. Consider this advice from a veteran...
５年…　あるいは１０年か
You didn't notice when I stole this, and you didn't notice when I walked past you.
それのみに没頭したのだ
Bastard... Return my Hunter License!
己を高めんがため 捧げ続けた長き時
Understand now?
その成果　しかと受け取った。
You still lack something.
これだけ打って　ほぼ無傷かい
Come with me.
まっ　予想通りだがな
I'll be your teacher.
いち個が。 修練の末　届き得る限界。
The real exam has only just begun.
あっ？ あっぱれだ　褒めて遣わす。
Today, we'll determine which
class your aura falls within.
王の戦術は至極　単純であった
There's something forming in the water... You're a Conjurer.
攻め続けること
A Conjurer...
ネテロが唯一　王に勝る技
A type that specializes in
manifesting their auras.
「百式観音」もダメージを ほとんど受けないのであれば
I see... Ideally, I would have liked to
have been an Enhancer.
恐るるに足らず
Can't do anything about
what you're born with.
しょせんは　傀儡の拳 型通りの動作しかできぬ
You can still learn Enhancer techniques. I'll spend the day expounding in further detail.
既に見た掌打では　受けきれない 角度から攻撃すれば 新たな掌打を 繰り出すしかない道理
Let's say you have a 100% chance
of mastering Conjurer techniques.
奴が　さらに新しい掌打を 出さざるを得ない角度からの
From that, these are your odds of learning
the other techniques. Emitter 40%
Manipulator 60%
Specialist 0%
Hatsu Enhancer 60%
Transmuter 80%
Conjurer 100%
攻撃を導き出す
It doesn't matter if you're a quick study, you can never completely
master a different category.
無限に等しい数に及ぼう
Specialist is a unique category. You can't learn Specialist techniques.
だが　個には 必ず特有の呼吸がある
These are very distinct abilities that are genetic or naturally acquired by
growing up under extreme conditions.
無意識のうちに 好む型　嫌う型があり
So why is it in this specific position?
おのずと その者　独自の流れを形作る
Because the adjacent categories,
Conjurer and Manipulator, have the highest chance of
becoming Specialists later on.
呼吸の流れを つかめさえすれば 幾多ある技の枝から 奴が　どれを選択するかを探るは
In that respect, your chances
are better than most.
十分に可能！
Remember what you said earlier?
無数にそそり立つ針の穴から 正解を導き出し
I...
正確に糸の矢を貫き通し…
I need... enough power to fight on my own!
やって見せよう！
You are correct
余には叶う！ 老秋の兵士よ　頼むぞ
to assume that the fastest means to your
goal would be via Enhancer abilities.
頼むから　その前に 精魂　果ててくれるなよ？
The Enhancer category
is the most efficacious for bolstering offensive,
defensive, and healing capabilities.
フハハハ… 笑うかよ　まぁ わしも楽しんでるから
However, as a Conjurer, you can only learn Enhancer techniques
at about half of their original potency.
お互いさまだ あらゆる角度からの掌撃にも 最短で体勢を立て直し 反撃に転じて来よる
When you attempt to use an ability beyond
your capacity, this creates strain, which can weaken you, possibly fatally.
掌の選択を誤れば　その速度は
In order to consistently come out
on top, you need a stable power.
次なる「百式」を繰り出すまでの 間をも奪うだろう
Will the stable power gained through
mastery of Conjurer techniques
気を抜けば 拝む　その前に四肢もがれ
put me on equal footing
with master Enhancers?
勝負が決するということ…
The brief answer is that it would be difficult.
正確無比に 最善手を打ち続けるしかない
Enhancers employ strong offensive
and defensive abilities.
根気の勝負
Conjurers usually suffer from an
inclination toward one or the other.
それが尽きた時が 貴様の潮時
On the other hand, this makes them incredibly
strong under the correct circumstances.
…だと　思ってんだろ？ アリの王よ！
Pop quiz time.
)
Is it possible to conjure a sword
that can cut through anything?
詰めるもんなら詰んでみな 「百式の零」を見せてやるぜ！
That is impossible. Why? Because that exceeds the
bounds of human ability. Exactly.
数百　数千と重ねた打撃が わずかではあるが
So conjured weapons aren't as effective
as their physical counterparts, but you can't conjure anything omnipotent.
王の内部に 鈍い痛みを蓄えつつあった
You will need to reflect on what
it is that you wish to conjure. Failure is not acceptable.
しかし…
Because you will need an incredible amount
んっ！
to conjure a single object.
止血しろ　そして余の名を言え。
Learning Nen only took you half a year?
貴様は　よくやった 人間としてはな。
So, what kind of employer are you seeking? I have some information for you
regarding the spider.
どうした？ 早くせぬと失血で死ぬぞ。
I shall await you in Yorknew City,
on September 1st. I'm looking for someone who has a lot of
influence on the Yorknew auction.
笑わせんな。
The nature of the job itself is irrelevant.
ふん！
The Yorknew City auction...
ほう…。
Employers with a lot of influence generally post the more difficult jobs.
誰が死ぬって？
I doubt any of them will hire a
Hunter with zero experience.
ラッキーパンチで調子に乗んなよ。 勝負は　これからだ！
I see three of them...
全くもって感服する。
Three employers who will decide based on
the interview, rather than your record.
気力が　いささかも 衰えていないのは驚異だ。
And they're only looking for bodyguards.
だが　貴様が脚を失ったのは 半ば必然。
I'll give you descriptions,
so make your choice. The first one is a gun fanatic.
悪手とは言えぬまでも 正着ではない防御が招いた結果だ。
Specifically, he's looking for a Midget Corp.
Golsnake 55, Limited Edition, Series #001.
コムギとの対局が 予知のごとき先見を可能にした 貴様が無意識に嫌う型。
The second one is a collector of fine china. Wants Lord Corp. commemorative
plates from 1655 and 1657...
その存在が 本来　無限であるはずの選択に
The third one collects human trophies.
しるべを示すのだ。 次は　左腕をもらう。
Skin covered in snaking dragon tattoos, jellied infant skulls, etc. A fascinating hobby.
そこからの攻防は 時間にして １分に満たなかったが…
Chains? Yes, when I heard about conjuring, that was the first thing that came to mind.
これが…
Why's that?
生涯最後！
Because there's evil running
loose that needs to be
その覚悟で放った ネテロの「百式」は
chained down to hell.
互いの力量 精神の高揚と相まって…
Really, now? I have a feeling that you're
really chaining yourself down.
千を超える 拳のやりとりとなって
What do you know? Hey! Wait up!
両者の間に 無数の火花を生んだ
I'm your teacher! I'm not finished talking! Hold it right there!
そして　その瞬間は訪れた…
Conjuring ordinary chains is pointless!
わずかに現れる技の偏り
And conjuring unbreakable chains is impossible!
身を盾に　ネテロの拳を 受け続けることで　王は その先に見える かすかな光を探し出し
On September 1st, Yorknew City will host the
world's greatest auction.
そして…　たどり着いた
That's where the spider... Where the Phantom Troupe will appear.
さぁ　述べよ 余の名を。
You want me to introduce
you to an employer with connections to the Yorknew auction?
フフフ…。 アリの王。
Huh? I got the same request twice today. That's amusing.
腕がなけりゃ　祈れねえとでも？
The boy I just passed? You know him?
ほう…。
What?
祈りとは　心の所作
No. He is interested in the auction, too...
対象を優しく包み込み…
That twerp will only make
your dinner taste worse.
先日　キルアが数里も先から その殺気に気付き…
We'll give you the best night of your life. Unfortunately, I am not on a date.
進路を変えたほどの 精神統一の業を経て蓄積した
A job? This is my employer. I am his bodyguard. Bodyguard?
ネテロの渾身の全オーラを
That's a riot. This babe is a bodyguard?
目も　くらむ 恒星のごとき光弾に変え 撃ち放つ
I'd like you to guard my body.
無慈悲の　咆哮である
I don't guard ugly men.
あぁ…　ハァ　ハァ…。 あぁ…　ハァ…　あっ…。
Man, I'll have to find a new employer.
ハァ　ハァ…。
Such a splendid moon... There he is! Surrender!
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Return the corpse samples you stole! Don't you interrupt my work
or this splendid moon.
ハァ　ハァ…。
Enough fooling around!
Hands in the air!
ハァ…。
Tsk, I was on the verge of
another masterful poem.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
But you've ruined the moment.
んっ…。 まさに　個の極致。
"A splendid full moon
and pursuers as clumsy
as baboons could be."
素晴らしい一撃であった。
Yeah, don't worry. I can take care of you
「零」でさえも…
along with all of the dogs. You don't need to worry, Eliza.
生命の頂点に立つことを許された。
Yeah, it'll be fine. You can count on me.
たどり着いた　賜物。
I was sent here by the agency.
お主は人間の いち個であって　王でなく
My name is Kurapika.
全て余に集約されるよう 機能したキメラの生態に。
Welcome.
だが　繁殖に 人類を利することは　なくなった。
Please wait in here.
選定の際に数や質を考慮する。
I apologize for the wait.
貴様の孤独な戦いは 無駄ではなかったのだ。
Everyone has arrived, so we will now explain the contract.
もう決して 二度　言うことはないぞ。
I'll start by stating the requirements. I won't ask whether you have a License.
余の名を言え。
I'm only interested
フッ…　フフ…。
There's one month before the auction begins.
フフフ…　フッ。
Before then, you must find one item
from the list we will provide, and bring it here.
俺は… 一人じゃ　ねえ。
These are the data cards.
白旗を揚げたはずの 老人を見ていた
Hmm? What's wrong? You look pale.
何だ…　こいつは…
Ah, Kurta eyeballs? A-rank obtainment difficulty.
アリの王　メルエム。
get excited, their eyes turn scarlet... Shut up.
お前さんは 何にも分かっちゃいねえよ。
Not another word.
人間の底すらない悪意を。
You need only find one item from the list.
それは 王が初めて感じる恐怖だった
If you are successful, you will be hired, to begin training as a
bodyguard and a collector.
全てを絞り尽くし
Best of luck, then.
死を待つのみであるはずの 老人の言葉が
I will pass this test.
決して虚栄の類いではないと 思える根拠が
First I need to curry their favor,
and win their trust.
その顔に表れていた
The man talking was, most likely,
not the actual employer. That only illustrates the distance
between the boss and me...
あなたの心臓が 鼓動を止めれば
I shall reduce that distance to zero, until the employer feels that he
can trust me with his secrets...
これは作動します。
There are two things that
collectors always want.
地獄があるなら また会おうぜ
The second is colleagues to whom they
can brag about their collection. He must have connections to
other human parts collectors.
貴様は…
Collectors who share their
disgusting acquisitions, a network of the lowest scum.
そう　貴様は…
I'll worm my way in, so that I can eradicate them all.
技術さえ確立してしまえば 短期間での 大量生産が可能なことと
Kurapika pursues his quest
to avenge his brethren and to punish the Phantom Troupe.
爆煙の特異な姿から
He prepares to step onto a new battlefield.